Presenting the heir
of Dynasty Hotel...
My daughter,
Hannah Montano...
Song!
- [BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ALL APPLAUDING]
Hannah!
Thank you, Father.
Hey, you guys. I'm still me.
I'm still your silly old Hannah.
- [GIGGLES]
- [HANNAH] Come on.
[STAFF GIGGLING]
But, on a serious note...
I still want to thank
all of you.
I've learned a lot from you.
I saw how dedicated
and hardworking you all are.
And because of that,
Dynasty Hotel will no longer
shut down!
[ALL CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
You guys will get
to keep your jobs!
Hannah!
Thank you, Ha--
Madam Hannah.
I'm sorry for everything
I've done to you.
[CHUCKLING]
Madam, just call me Hannah.
It's not like we're strangers.
- [CHUCKLES]
- But for you,
we will now be conducting
anger management workshops
so we can avoid
any more slapping incidents
lest we get reported
for breaking labor laws.
- Is it really necessary?
- Absolutely.
[MURMURING]
You're no different.
You're two-faced.
- See?
- Sorry, friend.
- Peace. Love you!
- Alright.
- Love you!
- [GIGGLES]
[SABRINA] Can I give you a hug?
- Of course!
- Thanks!
Oh! Hup! [GIGGLING]
Thank you.
- [ALL APPLAUDING]
- [BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Sorry, friend.
- It's all good!
- I love you!
- [HANNAH GIGGLING]
You look gorgeous!
You look so much
like a princess! Gosh!
- [EXCITED CHATTER, APPLAUSE]
- [MUSIC TURNS SULLEN]
Hannah, we have to go now.
Oh. Yes, Father.
- [SABRINA] Bye-bye!
- [APPLAUDING]
(In Korean) We love you!
We love you!
Do your best, alright?
Bye, Princess Hannah!
I want to go to Korea too!
[SULLEN MUSIC CONTINUES]